Raheel Tesmiferium, can I get something off my chest?
Black fame and wealth are not synonymous
with black excellence.
Materialism was not our ancestors' wildest dreams
and social media influencers can't, nor should ever,
be our guiding light and measure of greatness.
21st century black excellence should still be rooted
in the liberation of our people.
Otherwise it's just capitalism masquerading
as the promised land.
Pure unadulterated facts.
Capitalist success is not a signifier of liberation for all.
It's not.
And it's not a signifier for someone being so much more connected
to their ancestors than someone else.
And we do this all the time.
We look at people who have reached a certain level of fame
and money and wealth and we say, wow, look at them.
Churches are even preaching that as a word.
Don't get me wrong, money is a delightful enabler,
but it will not save us if we don't know us.